7500 W Slaughter Ln, Apt 6212, Austin, USA, 78749 Chaseostien@gmail.com 9564075093

# **CHASE OSTIEN**

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a Facilities Lead with 2 years of experience in overseeing in-person operations, building maintenance, security, and project management. I recently completed a Full Stack Software Development Bootcamp through UT Austin, gaining proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, MongoDB/Mongoose, Node.js, MySQL/Sequelize, GraphQL and Git.

### LINKS

<u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

Portfolio

## **SKILLS**

Facilities Management

Project Management

Operations Management

Office Administration

Workplace Culture

Vendor Management

React.js

Node.js

JavaScript

Express.js

MongoDB/Mongoose

MySQL/Sequelize

GraphQL

Git

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

NOV. 2022 - PRESENT

### Facilities Lead, Self Financial, Inc, Austin, Texas

- Overseeing in-person operations, building maintenance, security, and project management.
- Managing projects related to office renovations, moves, and real estate transactions.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to develop and execute strategies to optimize facilities operations and improve overall efficiency.

NOV, 2021 - NOV, 2022

# Operations Coordinator, Self Financial, Inc, Austin, Texas

- Overseeing office and building operations, people operations, and employee perks.
- Managing vendors, front desk staff, and general office administration.
- Assisting in implementing employee programs to improve workplace culture.

JAN. 2021 - OCT. 2021

# Customer Success Specialist, Self Financial, Inc, Austin, Texas

- Resolving customer account challenges through email, phone, and chat.
- Educating customers on Self's products and mission.
- Develop and implement customer success strategies to drive customer satisfaction and retention rates in the financial services industry.

# **EDUCATION**

AUG, 2015 - DEC, 2020

# Bachelor's Degree in Biology, Texas State University, San Marcos, Texas

Minor in Biochemistry.

### Facility Management Professional (FMP), IFMA

International Facility Management Association (IFMA)

Obtained the IFMA's Facility Management Professional certification

JUN, 2023 - NOV, 2023

# Full Stack Software Development Bootcamp, The University of Texas At Austin - CPE, Austin, Texas

Full Stack Software Development Completion Date: November 29th, 2023.